WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 11/1/1979; wsyr_radio_797; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
    Highlights: First Automatic Switchboard Opens; Will Rogers Day in Oklahoma; Election Day; Montana Becomes Our 41st State; Veteran’s Day; World War I Ends; Peanut Butter Invented; Oklahoma Becomes Our 46th State; USS California Launched; First Hot Air Balloon Flight; Thanksgiving Day; Director of Naval Aeronautics Established; First Streetcar Begins Operations; First Successful Launching of an Aircraft From a U. S. Navy Ship; First Photo Advertisement Printed; Sadie Hawkins Day; First Color Supplement Added to a Newspaper
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 12/1/1979; wsyr_radio_798; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 42)
    Highlights: First Western Movie; First U. S. Navy Flying School Opens; Navy Air Ferry Command Established; Napoleon Wins Greatest Victory; Monroe Doctrine Proclaimed; First Heart Transplant Operation; Environmental Protection Agency Becomes Effective; 21st Amendment Adopted; AFL and CIO Merge [American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations]; Finland Celebrates Independence; Pearl Harbor Bombed; First Daily Newspaper Founded; Mississippi Becomes 20th State; Spanish-American War Ends; U. S. Navy Publishes First Oceanography Text; First Motel Opens
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 1/1/1980; wsyr_radio_799; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
    Highlights: Michigan Admitted as 26th State; First Squadron of Continental Navy Put to Sea; Longest Railroad Tunnel in U. S. Opens; First State University Chartered; Prohibition Penalties Reduced; First Modern Torpedo Vessel Launched; National Geographic Society Founded; First Commercial Telephone Exchange Opens; Naturalization Act Passed; First U. S. Navy Seaplane Flight Completed; Gold Reserve Act Passed; Baseball’s American League Founded; U. S. Navy’s First Ironclad Warship Launched; Alaska Admitted as 49th State; U. S. Navy Uses Aircraft for the First Time
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 2/1/1980; wsyr_radio_800; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
    Highlights: First U. S. Navy Hospital Established; Presidential Succession Act Passed; National Freedom Day; Savannah Georgia Founded; 16th Amendment Goes Into Effect; Navy WWII Planes Bomb Tokyo; Four Chaplains Memorial Day; Battle Hymn of the Republic First Published; 11th Amendment Ratified; U. S. Navy Secretary Roosevelt Orders Philippine Attack; French and Indian War Ends; Republic of China Proclaimed; First Woman Appointed to California Supreme Court; U. S. Navy’s Hornet Sinks British Sloop Peacock; Puerto Rico Becomes a U. S. Commonwealth; ASCAP Established
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 4/1/1980; wsyr_radio_801; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
    Highlights: U. S. Occupies Okinawa; First U. S. Weather Satellite Launched; U. S. Navy Commander Peary Finds North Pole; First U. S. Mint Established; Congress Authorizes Design of American Flag; NATO [North Atlantic Treaty Organization] Formed; Civil War Begins; Los Angeles founded; Pullman railcar patented; Battle of Shiloh; Safety Pin invented; First U. S. Navy sub commissioned; Texas annexed to U. S.; Jefferson Memorial dedicated; Paul Revere rides; Lee surrenders; Curries [sic] discover radium; First electrically-powered U. S. Navy battleship launched
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 5/1/1980; wsyr_radio_802; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
    Highlights: Columbus discovers Jamaica; First American Medical school founded; Al Capone goes to prison; U. S. Navy’s largest aircraft carrier commissioned; U. S. Navy Seal adopted; Napoleon begins exile; Carnegie Hall opens; First Liger born; Manhattan Island purchased from Indians; WWII ends; U. S. Navy Wasp defeats British Betsy; Mother’s Day designated; Glacier National Park Established; U. S. Navy Commander Byrd makes first North Pole Flight; Columbus dies; Lindbergh begins trans-Atlantic flight; First U. S. Navy Secretary appointed
  - The Spirit of Navy: What in the World Happened?, 6/1/1980; wsyr_radio_803; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 43)
    Highlights: U. S. Navy motto adopted; Hurricane season begins; American Indians granted U. S. citizenship; Marconi patents wireless radio; First U. S. Navy Aircraft carrier commissioned; D-Day; Landmark Day; First U. S. Navy Academy graduation; Philippine Independence; Magna Carta sealed; U. S. Navy victorious in Battle of Midway; Franklin discovers electricity; Arkansas admitted to Union; 12th Amendment ratified; Battle of Bunker Hill; Federal Communications Commission established; Battle of Waterloo; Alaskan pipeline begin operations
  - The United States Navy Band, Commander Charles Brendler, conductor, wsyr_radio_440; VinylDisc
    Side 1: The United States Navy Band: 1 - The star spangled banner; 2 - British National anthem; 3 -French National anthem; 4 - An American fantasie (Herbert); Side 2: 5 - Anchors Aweigh (Zimmerman); 6 - Armed Forces medley; 7 - The stars and stripes forever (Sousa)
  - The World at Noon; Classics in recordings, 07/14/1947; wsyr_radio_434; Lacquer discs/acetates
    No labels. Note from old sleeve reads: "For July 14"; "Espana Cani"; "Pawanne"; "Dark Eyes"
  - Thirtieth - Thirtieth First Anniversary Program Cross Roads with Rabbi Beny Friedman and Father Fr. Shannon, Don Dauer, host, 12/06/1964; wsyr_radio_972; includes synopsis with handwritten notes in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:30 (Box 56)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 126-141, 05/07/1982; wsyr_radio_575; includes MLB postcard and format sheet; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 142-157, 05/27/1982; wsyr_radio_576; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 158-173, 06/21/1982; wsyr_radio_577; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 174-188, 07/13/1982; wsyr_radio_578; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 189-203, 07/30/1982; wsyr_radio_579; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 21)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 204-218, 08/20/1982; wsyr_radio_580; includes MLB postcard; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 219-228, 09/10/1982; wsyr_radio_581; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - This Date In Baseball History - Shows 229-238, 09/23/1982; wsyr_radio_582; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - Time keeper Aircheck - President Truman dead, Ed Murphy, wsyr_radio_597; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Tip Off Achievement Award Dinner; Bill Everett, Host., wsyr_radio_456; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11)
  - Tip-Off Awards (Original), 03/17/1964; wsyr_radio_943; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 53)
  - Tip-Off Awards (tape 2), 03/17/1968; wsyr_radio_945; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 13:00 (Box 54)
  - Tip-Off Awards Banquet (FTM 10-10:30) (No. 2), 03/13/1972; wsyr_radio_946; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 30:00 (Box 54)
  - Tip-Off Awards Banquet (FTM 10-10:30) (No. 3), 03/13/1972; wsyr_radio_947; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 12:00 (Box 54)
  - Tip-Off Dinner Awards, Rhea Eckel, 03/17/1963; wsyr_radio_944; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 54)
  - Tolley Special: A Conversation With Chancellor Tolley, 05/11/1969; wsyr_radio_901; box includes note from Ron Hasings [Hastings?]; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 53:45 (Box 50)
  - Tribute To Deacon Doubleday (Bob), 1911-1971 (part 1 of 2), 02/24/1971; wsyr_radio_464; WSYR Radio, Dan Daver, host; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Tribute To Deacon Doubleday (Bob), 1911-1971 (part 2 of 2), 02/24/1971; wsyr_radio_465; WSYR Radio, Dan Daver, host; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Tribute to Frank McGee, 04/17/1974; wsyr_radio_1021; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 8:30 (Box 59)
  - Truman - Foreign Policy (part 2), 10/17/1950; wsyr_radio_373; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman - Foreign Policy (parts 1 and 3), 10/17/1950; wsyr_radio_372; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman - UN Address on 5th United Nations Day (part 1), 10/24/1950; wsyr_radio_374; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman - UN Address on 5th United Nations Day (part 2), 10/24/1950; wsyr_radio_375; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman and Churchill at Westminster college (parts 1 and 3), 03/05/1946; wsyr_radio_296; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman and Churchill at Westminster college (parts 2 and 4), 03/05/1946; wsyr_radio_297; side 2 has damaged label; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman and Churchill at Westminster college (parts 5 and 6), 03/05/1946; wsyr_radio_298; side 2 has damaged label; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Truman and Marshall; President Truman, part 2, 11/26/1945; 01/03/1946; wsyr_radio_058; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 10)
    A-President Truman awards General George C. Marshall the Distinguished Service Award. General Marshall delivers his farewell address. All music played by the U. S. Army Band. Don Fisher disc has proceedings for NBC. Q. T. H. - Inner courtyard of the Pentagon, Washington D. C.; B- President Truman radio address (part 2)
  - Truman and McArthur issue, 1951; wsyr_radio_051; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
    A-1 and 2: from "Old soldier is…", speech to Congress; A-3: President Truman/ Radio address, firing of MacArthur. All excerpts from speeches (1951). Cut 1 & 2 - MacArthur (Fade away); 3 - Truman (Fires)
  - Truman General, 12/27/1972; wsyr_radio_976; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - Truman’s Oath and end Truman’s inauguration speech (part 3), 01/20/1949; wsyr_radio_355; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Tuesday Productions Inc., wsyr_radio_601; includes business card of Shirley Ferris, Manager, Program sales; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Tuesday Productions Inc., wsyr_radio_602; includes business card of Shirley Ferris, Manager, Program sales; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - TV Audio Dub - Special Program - Prisons: Attica - Report (Edited for Radio), 03/19/1978; wsyr_radio_546; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:45 (Box 19)
  - Twentieth Century Leaders, Program No. 1 (10:05-11 PM), voice tracks of Professor Stephen P. Koff (part 1 & 2), 09/12/1976; wsyr_radio_912; part 1 - 18:05; part 2 - 19:30; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 55:00 (Box 51)
  - Twentieth Fourth Le Moyne College Commencement Exercises (2), 05/18/1974; wsyr_radio_904; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 90:00 (Box 50)
  - U. S. Army: Mountain Infantry Drive, Amos rice - ESSO credits; West Point Anniversary Program (part 2), 03/13/1943; 03/14/1943; wsyr_radio_208; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - United Nations, Conference opening - San Francisco, parts 1 and 3; Translation [of] Molotov’s speech, part 2, 04/25/1945; 04/26/1945; wsyr_radio_062; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
  - University College Course program 10 "What Makes Government Work", 03/29/1981; wsyr_radio_561; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 55:00 (Box 20)
  - University College Discussion of Twelfth Night (part 1 & 2), 12/19/1976; wsyr_radio_909; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 45:35 (Box 51)
  - University College Independent Study Degree Program, 01/16/1977; wsyr_radio_907; Ruth Sisley, moderator, Don DeSalvia, staff, Zermaine Breuderlagh [?], Damon Kanebrew, Esther Salomon, Glenn Chase, students; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 104:15 (Box 51)
  - University College Program 12 "What Makes Government Work", 04/12/1981; wsyr_radio_562; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 55:00 (Box 20)
  - University College Special - WSYR - "Mentally Retarded Adults", 06/20/1979; 07/22/1979; wsyr_radio_477; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 53:20 (Box 14)
    Announcer: Alan Milair, Mrs. Bernice Schultz, Mr. Guy Caruso, Mr. Keith Patrick. Interview Conducted by Mr. Robert E. Cecil, assistant dean of University College, President Syracuse Board of Education
  - University College Special Program - Gardening Landscaping (parts 1 and 2), 03/06/1977; wsyr_radio_906; moderator: Kit Sime, guests: Walt Newhouser and Doc Watson, includes transcripts and handwritten notes in box; note on label reads: Part I - 23:00; Part II - 22:20; tape does not include intros and outros; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 45:20 (Box 51)
  - University College: Personal Problems of The Elderly, 01/09/1976; 01/09/1977; wsyr_radio_908; Dr. Hidde Van Duym, moderator, guests: Mrs. Ruth Sam, Rs. Helen Anderson, Dr. Tony J. Livinsky, psychiatric; box includes additional notes about participants; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 49:30 (Box 51)
  - Unknown; President Truman (part 3), 10/23/1945; wsyr_radio_288; label on side 1 is damaged; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], wsyr_radio_590; sticker on box is # 28, sticker on reel is #2; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - [unknown]; London Weekend (part 4), wsyr_radio_314; Lacquer discs/acetates
    1 - RCA Victor - "Music America loves best", Robert Merrill, RCA Victor Orchestra, Frank Black, Cond., Kenneth Bangleart, host, June 1946, First part. 2 - RCA Victor show "Music America loves best", Part 2, Lewis - Kahn fight, televised, ends with chimes. Trip to London, England, E. R. V. and Vern Cook, Chas. Wheaton taking off, Bill Rothram, narrator
  - Up Reach Radio: Up Reach Audition program, wsyr_radio_932; note in box reads, "Up Reach was recently selected as one of the nations top five programs in The International Radio Festival of New York and is currently programmed on over 250 radio stations, nationwide."; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 3:00 (Box 53)
  - US Air Force: Aircraft Observer Announcements, 09/20/1955; wsyr_radio_424; handwritten note on label reads: "Hold for sound effects"; VinylDisc
    Side 1: Cuts 1 & 2 - Announcement No. 1; Cuts 3 & 4 - Announcements No. 2; Cuts 5 & 6 - Announcements No. 3; Cuts 7 & 8 - Announcements No. 1A; Cuts 9 & 10- Announcements No. 2A; Cuts 11 & 12 - Announcements No. 3A; Side 2: Cuts 1 & 2 - Announcements No. 4; Cuts 3 & 4 - Announcements No. 5; Cuts 5 & 6 - Announcements No. 6; Cuts 7 & 8 - Announcements No. 4A; Cuts 9 & 10 - Announcements No. 5A; Cuts 11 & 12 - Announcements No. 6A
  - V-J Day announcement; V-J Day in Syracuse, 08/13/1945; wsyr_radio_238; Side 2 has damaged label; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vadeboncoeur - Colonel [Harry C.] Wilder interview (part 1), 09/29/1945; wsyr_radio_287; Harry C. Wilder was the founder and president of WSYR; note on label reads: "Ret. to Merrick."; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vadeboncoeur - Colonel Harry C. Wilder interview (part 2), 09/29/1945; wsyr_radio_285; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vadeboncoeur Christmas Story; Floyd Ottaway Intro, Dec 1966; wsyr_radio_1015; transcripts included in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:15 (Box 59)
  - Vadeboncoeur; Cpl. Johny Gates, Jean Carr marriage with interview by Mr. Wallace; 3 Spots, 05/19/1945; wsyr_radio_255; notes by audio engineer RJH read: "A2 - E. R. Vadeboncoeur: "Is Hitler alive or dead?" B: 3 Spots with jingles for Rudolph’s Jewelers-Opticians."; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vadeboncouer. [International] Harvester; Patterson & McDonald (part 1), 10/31/1940; 11/01/1940; wsyr_radio_142; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vandeboncoeur and Wheaton from London; "Eton", 07/08/1946; wsyr_radio_315; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vandeboncoeur and [Charles] Wheaton from London - "Hatfield House", wsyr_radio_318; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Label damaged. Recorded from the shortwave. BBC broadcast E. R. Vandeboncoeur & Chas. Wheaton. One side - "Hatfield House". Chas w. winner of WSYR "New Horizon" contest. Ends w/ transition to Variety Band Boy", BBC program. Sounds like first broadcast of series.
  - Vandeboncoeur from London - Reception at English Speaking Union, 07/10/1946; wsyr_radio_319; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Vandeboncoeur interview with Janet Webb from London, Finsbury, 07/09/1946; wsyr_radio_317; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Record from the shortwave. Morning BBC broadcast - Janet Webb, Charles Wheaton & E. R.Vandeboncoeur. Rebroadcast by WSYR. Television from Alexandra Palace mentioned, (later destroyed during the WW2). Long side has talk complete. Short side has short second talk - ends with: Good afternoon, from London. "Mayor of Finsbury" by E. R. Vandeboncoeur".
  - Variety Victory Show, Murray Bernthal; RCA Show for Sunday - Music America loves best (part 2), 07/29/1945; 08/12/1945; wsyr_radio_427; some content is illegible; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - VE day - Allied generals from Paris (part 2); Our Nation’s Rations, Betty Crocker, host, 05/04/1945; 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_253; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - VE Day, President Truman and Churchill, part 1; VE Day, Allied Generals from Paris, part 1 (#8), 06/18/1940; 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_064; handwritten note on the sleeve reads: "Italian declaration of war, Mussolini, June 18, 1940". UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 10)
  - VE Day, Winston Churchill, part 2, 05/08/1945; wsyr_radio_065; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 10)
  - Vic and Sade; King and Queen visit to Congress (part 1), 06/05/1939; 06/09/1939; wsyr_radio_121; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Victory over Polio, parts 1 and 2, 04/21/1955; wsyr_radio_095; note on sleeve reads: "Historical File"; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 14)
    Floyd O'Howay, host. Salk Vaccine City Hospital, Syracuse, N. Y. Research Center, March of Dimes, Dr. Francis Thomas, Dr. Jonas Salk, Mrs. Genevieve Fahey, City Hospital Administrator.
  - Wainwright dinner in Skaneateles, NY - Start of Patterson’s speech (part 1); General [Jonathan Mayhew] Wainwright - News of the world, 09/17/1945; 09/25/1945; wsyr_radio_281; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Wainwright dinner, Skaneateles, NY - [Jonathan Mayhew] Wainwright speech, End of dinner (part 3), 09/25/1945; wsyr_radio_283; Damaged label.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Wainwright dinner, Skaneateles, NY - End of Patterson speech and beginning of Wainwright (part 2); Description of General [Jonathan Mayhew] Wainwright arrival Washington, 09/10/1945; 09/25/1945; wsyr_radio_282; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - War Bond Show, parts 1 and 3, 09/09/1943; wsyr_radio_027; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 4)
    A - WSYR Program/Prod.: "Service Stars Review" - 3rd War Loan Drive Show, part 1: Col. Howard Wilder introduces program: Johnny MC Andrews, M. C. Band plays "Price Charming", Navy - Samson Navel Station; B - part 3: Trio with Band "If that's the way you wanted baby", E. R. Vadeboncouer introduces Major Levi Chase Jr. (Cortland, N. Y.) Army Air Corps pilot
  - War Bond Show, parts 2 and 4, 09/09/1943; wsyr_radio_028; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 4)
    A - WSYR Program: "Service Stars Review", part 4: Major Chase (continues and concludes), piano Concerto in B flat Minor aka: "Tonight We Love", solo; B - Marine Private Leonard Antonio and Seaman Sam Vaughn are interviewed. Band plays "Little Did I know"
  - War Bond Show, parts 5 and 7, 09/09/1943; wsyr_radio_022; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 3)
    War Bond Show (Parts 5 and 7), 3rd War Loan Drive. Series Stars Revue. A - Part 5: Piano Boogie Woogie piece songs, Trio and Orchestra "Deed I do", E. R. Vadeboncouer (E. R. V.) introduced by Major Chase who introduces Lt. Tobin, then E. R. V. introduces Eking of the United Press; B 1 - Part 7: Fred Jeske introduced Johnny Band Andrews, Timekeeper show. Fred introduces Lucille Manners, soprano at the Cities Service Oil Program, who sings: "Siboney" with orchestra then "Sweet mystery of Life" with piano accompaniment
  - War Bond Show, parts 6 and 8, 09/09/1943; wsyr_radio_023; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 3)
    A - Part 6: Ekins talk concludes. Mr. John L. Haley, War Finance Committee of Onondaga County speaks; B - Part 8: National Anthem sung by Lucille Manners with stage guests and audience with orchestra. Lincoln Auditorium Central Technical High School, Syracuse, N. Y.
  - War Crisis (part 2), Kerr, Hillman, etc.; Larry Clinton Orchestra, 08/27/1939; wsyr_radio_120; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - War Memorial park dedication (part 1), 10/22/1949; wsyr_radio_363; recorded by WNDR radio station for WSYR; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - War Memorial park dedication (part 2), 10/22/1949; wsyr_radio_364; recorded by WNDR radio station for WSYR; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - WFBG: Pete McCoy; Dup. Serv. Div. (DM-433), Tr. 2-7711; PAA-Third Quarter-RB 80540 - D, 1969; wsyr_radio_1030; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 3:00 (Box 59)
    1 - Why Plymouth - F, PAA 69-18 (0:60); 2 - Why Plymouth - C, PAA 69-19 (0:60); 3 - Why Plymouth - F & C, PAA 69-20 (0:60)
  - What in the world happened?, Dec 1977; wsyr_radio_543; Navy recruiting piece; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - What in the world happened?, Mar 1979; wsyr_radio_554; from Navy Recruiting Command; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - What in the world happened?, May 1979; wsyr_radio_555; from Navy Recruiting Command; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - "Willow Herb" - Vandeboncoeur, 07/09/1946; 07/10/1946; wsyr_radio_316; Side 2 is illegible.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Wilson Lawless and Nowakowski, wsyr_radio_617; syndicated program; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
    Bob Euringham - dairy farmer from Lafayettte, NY; "Vote for Malcom Wilson, Governor" - Political Endorsements
  - Winston Churchill, wsyr_radio_439; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1 - NBC Special program - England Winston Churchill, BBC broadcast. "Recent illness" - "When Peace comes - war was still on. Post war and Domestic Issues. Side 2: starts w/ "in the politics and economics in our society. Ends w/ "more sensitle than before
  - Winston Churchill - "After fall of France" (part 1); "I love a mystery" (part 2), 06/13/1940; 06/18/1940; wsyr_radio_139; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - "After fall of France" (part 2); "I love a mystery" (part 1), 06/13/1940; 06/18/1940; wsyr_radio_140; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - "Appeal to France"; [Raymond] swing, 10/21/1940; wsyr_radio_141; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - "Canadian Parliament" (parts 1 and 3), 12/30/1941; wsyr_radio_169; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - "Canadian Parliament" (parts 2 and 4), 12/30/1941; wsyr_radio_170; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - 2nd year anniversary of Prime Minister (part 2), 05/10/1942; wsyr_radio_177; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - 2nd year anniversary of Prime Minister (parts 1 and 3), 05/10/1942; wsyr_radio_176; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - Review of war (part 1 and 3), 05/13/1945; wsyr_radio_250; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill - Review of war, Part 2; RCA Music America loves best (part 2), 05/13/1945; wsyr_radio_251; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill (part 1 number 2), 12/23/1940; wsyr_radio_145; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill (part 1); Defense for America (part 1), 08/24/1941; 08/23/1941; wsyr_radio_157; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill (part 2); Defense for America (part 2), 08/24/1941; 08/23/1941; wsyr_radio_158; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill (part 5), 03/31/1949; wsyr_radio_358; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill (parts 1 and 3), 03/31/1949; wsyr_radio_356; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill (parts 2 and 4), 03/31/1949; wsyr_radio_357; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill address to Congress; [unknown], 01/17/1952; wsyr_radio_393; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill eulogizes King George; [unknown], 02/06/1952; wsyr_radio_394; note on sleeve reads: "Sat. Evening Post".; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Winston Churchill on the Fall of Poland; "Shadow" Program 167 (part 2), 10/01/1939; wsyr_radio_123; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Winston] Churchill - Address to Congress (part 1, side 3), 12/26/1941; wsyr_radio_168; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Winston] Churchill (part 2); "Shadow", Program 167 (part 2), 10/01/1939; 10/31/1939; wsyr_radio_133; Lacquer discs/acetates